A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Program and Policy, SG 3.5 FA1843
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Program and Policy, SG 3.5
1913-2017
1960-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA1843
156.04 Cubic Feet 396 containers
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for research in accordance with the 2022 terms of deposit, with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact a RAC archivist.
Scope and Contents
This material consists of administrative and program and policy information in the form of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, meetings, evaluations, reviews, and reports.
Arrangement
Arranged in original order, in series and subseries, primarily by subject/topic.
- Audiovisual Materials, 1; 5.26 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  Moving Images; Sound recordings
  - Program and Policy - General (No Program Letter) - Audiovisual Materials, 1.900
    - History - Ken on the History of the Foundation, 1994 June; 1 VHS (Box T3)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - History - Program Lunch - RF History in Eastern Europe, 1999 October 27; 1 VHS (Box T3)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th - RF Staff Centennial Video Files, 1 DVD (Box T4)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th - RF Centennial Reception in Bangkok, 2013 January 31; 1 DVD (Box T4)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th - Visit to Siriraj Hospital, 2013 January 29; 1 DVD (Box T4)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th - Listing of Digitized Films, 2013; 15 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th - Beijing Centennial Events (Reception, Opening Ceremony, etc.), 2013; 1 DVD (Box T4)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 90th - Supplementary Material, 2002 December 4; Audio cassette (Box T2)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 75th - RWL Comments at Anniversary Party, 1988 May 13; 1 audio cassette (Box T2)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 75th - "The Rockefeller Foundation 75th Anniversary", 1988 September 13; 2 audio cassettes (Box T2)
    - Program and Policy - CAW Panel Discussions, Images, 2009-2010; 3 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Civil Society - Quest for Change: Civil Society in the Middle East, 1 VHS; 27 minutes, 18 seconds (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture - Artist Summit - Part I - Opening Remarks and Keynote Address, 1996 April 27; VHS (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture - Artist Summit - Part II - The Artist in the Community, 1996 April 27; VHS (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture - Artist Summit - Part III - Public Influence Over Artists Expression, 1996 April 27; VHS (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture - Artist Summit - Part IV - Artists' Private Feelings and Public Expression, 1996 April 27; VHS (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Creativity and Culture (2005 CC 029) - Creative Photos, NY, 2006 April 4; 1 CD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth - eHealth Week 1-4, 4 CD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth Interviews from the RF eHealth Conference, 2008 Summer; 1 DVD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - eHealth - Bellagio eHealth Call to Action - Bishop Tutu Video, 1 DVD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Equal Opportunity (EO) - Theories of Change Meeting, 1998 March 11; 2 audio cassettes (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security - USDA Millennium Lecture: Elimination of Global Hunger - Eileen Kennedy, Dan Glickman, Gordon Conway, 2000 September 25; 1 VHS (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Food Security - Officers Review Meeting - Food Security: Science Technology Sub-Theme, 2000 May 9; 1 CD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Global Environmental Program - Political Economy of Water (Master), 1998 November 9; 1 audio cassette (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative - Retreat, 2012 May; 3 CDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Informal City Dialogues - Trailer and Slides, 2013 November; 3 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Informal City Dialogues - Website, 2013 March 27; 1 CD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Information Policy, 1997 January 27; 1 audio cassette (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Intellectual Property Rights - RF Intellectual Property Brochure, Text Images from Web, 1 CD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - NATC - OM and Board of Trustees (BOT) Presentations, 2003; 1 CD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - New Orleans - "When the Levees Broke: A Requiem in Four Acts", DVD (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - New York City (NYC) Opportunities Fund - Jane Jacobs Medal Awards Event, 2008-2011; 5 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Pandemics - Disease Surveillance Network Convening, Nairobi, Kenya, 2011 May 23-25; 2 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Africa - The Rockefeller Foundation and Africa in the New Millennium, Parts 1, 2, 3, 2000 March; 2 VHS (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Africa - Pictures of RF Work in Africa, Rwanda, Kenya, 10 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Africa - ARO Grant Meeting, 1 CD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Africa - African Grantees Convening, 2012 August; 3 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Regional Activities - Southeast Asia - Southeast Regional Program and Africa Regional Program, 2002 March 13; 1 VHS; 34 minutes (Box T1)
    - Program and Policy - Resilience - Event - Looping Show, Ripple Effects, Images, 2012 September 25; 1 DVD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Rockefeller Global Urban Summitt, 3 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - School Reform - Supplementary Materials - Seminar on Public Commitment to Education, Rockefeller Foundation, 1999 March 17; 4 audio cassettes (Box T1)
    - Program and Policy - Seal - RF Logos, Templates, Guidelines, 2 CDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Social Investing - Impact Investment Exchange Asia (Video, Audio, Photos), 2 DVDs (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Special Programming - Chris Colchough: Education Policy in Africa (Master), 1998 September 24; 1 audio cassette (Box T1)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - The Rockefeller Foundation: The Next Five Years, 2 VHS (Box T1)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - The Rockefeller Foundation: The Next Five Years - George Conway and Lincoln Chen Presentation, 1999 June 9; 1 VHS (Box T1)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Nanotechnology - Meeting Materials - International Workshop of Nanotechnology Commodities and Development, 1 DVD (Box T4)
    - Program and Policy - Supplementary Material - Open Mind, WNET TV - Peter Goldmark Interview, 1 VHS (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Supplementary Material - Staff Breakfast with Judith Rodin, 2005 March 2; 1 VHS (Box T3)
      Scope and Contents
      Wednesday
    - "Bill Gates and the Rockefeller Foundation", 60 Minutes 2, CBS TV, 2000 December 5; 1 VHS; 13 minutes (Box T3)
    - Program and Policy - Urban Institute Challenges - Reference Group Meeting, 2012 November 29; 1 DVD (Box T4)
      Restricted - Open in 2032
    - Program and Policy - Working Communities (WC) - "CSH Supportive Housing: It Works" - Supportive Housing Leadership Forum II, Georgetown University, 2005 November 14-15; 1 CD (Box T4)
  - Members and Meetings - Audiovisual Materials, 1.903
    - Members and Meetings - Supplementary Material - Alice Stone Ilchman Retirement Luncheon, 200 December 12; 2 VHS (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - Supplementary Material - Rockefeller Trustee Video, 39:02, PAL (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - Supplementary Material - Rockefeller Trustee Videos (Revised), 2003 April; 2 VHS (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - Supplementary Material - Board Meeting, 2001 September; CD (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - Supplementary Material - Staff Awards Ceremony - Ela Bhatt's Farewell, 2003 April 23; 3 audio cassettes (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - Supplementary Material - Staff Awards Ceremony - Ela Bhatt's Farewell, 2003 April 23; 1 VHS (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - Ken Prewitt Presentation, June 2000 Board Meeting - 2000 Census, 2000 June; Audio cassette (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - Board Asia Trip - HRH Reception, 2000 September; 2 VHS (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - Kykuit Retreat, 1994; 2 VHS and 2 DVD (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - June Board Meeting 2000, 2000 June; 1 audio cassette (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - India/Indonesia Trip, Board of Trustees, 1994; 1 VHS (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - India/Indonesia Trip, Board of Trustees, 1994; 1 audio casssette (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - India/Indonesia Trip, Board of Trustees, 1994; 3 floppy discs (Box T1)
    - Members and Meetings - 2004 Kenya and Uganda Trip - The Rockefeller and Makerere University Over the Years, 2 VHS (Box T2)
    - Members and Meetings - Pocantico Board Retreat - Part I, 2000 March 27; 1 VHS (Box T2)
    - Members and Meetings - Pocantico Board Retreat - Part II, 2000 March 27; 1 VHS (Box T2)
  - Arts and Humanities - Audiovisual Materials, 1.929
    - Program and Policy - Arts and Humanities (AH) Retreat, 1998 May 9; 5 audio cassettes (Box T2)
    - Program and Policy - Development History Meeting, 1990 July 16; 2 audio cassettes (Box T2)
    - Program and Policy - Media Worldwide - Douglas Davis, 1991 August 4; 1 VHS (Box T2)
- Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 12.62 Cubic Feet 32 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
  - Administration - Minutes - Consultancies, 1978-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2075
  - Administration - Minutes - Consultancies, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2077
  - Administration - Minutes - Consultancies, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Administration, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Administration, 1977-1978 March (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Administration, 1978 April-December (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Administration, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Administration, 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Administration, 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Administration, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Administration, 1995-2000 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Administration, 2001-2006 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
  - Administration, 2006-2013 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Administration - Supplementary Material, c. 1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Administration - Supplementary Material, c. 1970 (Box 14, Folder 1-2, Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary File - Photographs, c. 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Administration - Supplementary File - Poems, c. 1970 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Administration - Supplementary File - Reviewers, 1997-2007 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2048
  - Administration - Bellagio Create Artists Fellowship Program, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Administration - Ella Holbrook Walker (Princess Della Torre E Tesso), 1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Administration - Ella Holbrook Walker Fellows (Consultancies), 1999-2006 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Fellowships - Open in 2027
  - Administration - Ella Holbrook Walker Fellows - A-J, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Administration - Ella Holbrook Walker Fellows - K-Z, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Administration - Frati Reconstruction, 1990-2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Administration - Frati Reconstruction - Supplementary Material, c. 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Administration - Woodlot "Bellagio Woodlot", 1976-1982, c. 2000 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    Restricted - Property - Open in 2030
  - Administration - Inventories and Appraisals, 1975-2007 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Property - Open in 2038
  - Administration - Inventory and Valuation of Furniture and Furnishings, c. 2007 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Villa Serbelloni Administration - Inventory and Appraisals, c. 2014 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Property - Open in 2045
  - Villa Serbelloni Administration - Inventory and Appraisals, c. 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Property - Open in 2039
  - Administration - Legal Issues, 1971-1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Administration - Tower, 1981-2001 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Property - Open in 2032
  - Administration - Trustees at Bellagio, 1977-1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Administration - Villa Staff Issues, 1971-2013 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2084
  - Anniversary - 50th, 2008-2009 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Bellagio Committee Decisions, 1999-2006 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Bellagio Committee Decisions, 1973-1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Finance, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Finance, 1979-1996 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - Bellagio Management Audit, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Executive Search - Open 2036
  - Renovation, 1981-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Property - Open in 2027
  - Travel, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Program and Policy, 1969-1978 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Program and Policy, 1978-2009 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
  - Program and Policy, 2004-2013 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy, 2004-2013 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2074
  - Program and Policy - Reports (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Program and Policy - Outreach/Virtual Bellagio Community, 2010-2013 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Program and Policy - General, 900; 89.85 Cubic Feet 233 containers
  - Program and Policy - General (No program letter)
    - Office Space - Renovation - Folk Art Collection, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Agreements - A-D, c. 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Agreements - E-J (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Agreements - K-S (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Agreements - T-Z (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Office Space - 420 Fifth Avenue Furniture, 1991-2012 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Property - Open in 2043
    - Administration, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - All-Staff Memos, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Decorations, 1982-2011 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Disaster Recovery, 1999-2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Disaster Recovery, 2004-2012 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2083
    - Documents of Record, 1913-2004 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Executive Team, 2009-2012 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2053
    - Financial Administration - Minutes, 1951-1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Financial Administration - Minutes, 1992-2012 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Financial Administration, 1971-1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Financial Administration, 1990-2013 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Treasurer/Development - Open in 2034
    - Financial Administration - Auditors, 1971-2017 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Confidential material
    - Financial Administration - Bank Accounts, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Financial Administration - Budget, 1993-2012 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Treasurer/Development - Open in 2033
    - Financial Administration - Corporate Responsibility, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Development - Open in 2030
    - Financial Administration - Credit Facility, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Financial Administration - Endowment, 1998-2009 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Financial Administration - Investment Council, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Financial Administration - Investments - Real Estate, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Financial Administration - Taxation, 1990-2011 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Financial Administration - Taxation - Investments, 1995-2001 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Financial Administration - Taxation - Sales Tax, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Financial Administration - Taxation - Reports, 1917-1954 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Financial Administration - Taxation, 1970-1973 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Financial Administration - Taxation, 1974-1989 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Ford-Rockefeller Seminar Series, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Grant Tracking, 1982, 1984-1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Financial Administration - Treasurer, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2041
    - History - Latin America, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - History - Field Offices, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - History - Domestic Education, c. 2005 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - History - Historical Funding Details - Supplementary File, c. 2006 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - History, 1998-2005 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - History, 2006-2007 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - History, 2008-2012 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - History, 2013-2022 (Box 47, Folder 2, Box 48, Folder 1-2)
      Restricted - Open in 2033
    - History - Schools of Public Health, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - History - Supplementary Material - 100th Anniversary Centennial Series, 2013 (Box 388, Folder 3-4, Box 389, Folder 1-4)
    - Management of Advisory Functions, 2006-2007 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Office Space - Ergonomics, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Officers - Photographs, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Officers, 1971-1982 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Officers, 1982-1993 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Officers - Reports, 1950-1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Officers - Reports, 1970s-1980s (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Officers - Reports, 1999-2010 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Officers - Operating Officer (COO), 2005-2013 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Officers - Presidential Search, 1996-2004 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2045
    - Officers - Program Lunches, 2003-2013 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Officers - Meeting Notes, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Officers - Signatory Powers, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Organization - Front of File, c. 1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2057
    - Organization, 2010-2012 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Organization, 1960-2009 (Box 54, Folder 1-4)
    - Organization - Operations, 2006-2011 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2082
    - Organization - Anniversary, 1983-1998 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Organization - Anniversary, 1983-1998 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2069
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th, 2009-2011 (Box 381, Folder 4-5, Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th, 2012-2014 (Box 382, Folder 2-4, Box 383, Folder 1)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th, 2012-2014 (Box 375, Folder 5)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2085
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th - Beijing Health Summit, 2013 (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 100th - Supplementary Material - Publications, 2013 (Box 383, Folder 3-4, Box 384, Folder 1-3)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 90th - Supplementary Material, 2003 (Box 384, Folder 4)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 80th and 85th - Supplementary Material, 1993, 1998 (Box 385, Folder 1-3)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 85th Anniversary Party - Photo Album, 1998 (Box 392)
    - Organization - Anniversary - 75th - Supplementary Material, 1988 (Box 385, Folder 4, Box 386, Folder 1-3)
    - Program Team Meetings - Minutes, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Senior Leadership Team, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Minutes, 2001-2012 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy, 1983-1984 (Box 55, Folder 4, Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Pro. 71-76, 1981-1985 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy, 1989-1990 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Pro. 1E, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy, 1985-1988 (Box 57, Folder 2-3, Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy, 1991-1997 (Box 58, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy, 2000-2001 (Box 59, Folder 4, Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy, 2002-2011 (Box 60, Folder 3-4, Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy, 2012-2014 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Open in 2025
    - Program and Policy - Supplementary File, 1981-2011 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Action Groups - Career and Professional Development, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Action Groups - C.R.E.A.T.E., 2011 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Action Groups - Global Action Team, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Action Groups - Strategy and Vision, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Action Groups - Transparency and Decision-Making, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - African Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Agenda Setting, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Agra Markets Access, 2010 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Program and Policy - AIDS, 1987-2005 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Alliance for a Green Revolution in Africa, 2006-2010 (Box 63, Folder 2-3, Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Alliance for a Green Revolution in Africa, 2011-2016 (Box 64, Folder 2-4, Box 65, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Open in 2027
    - Program and Policy - Alliance for a Green Revolution in Africa - Supplementary File, 2007-2014 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Alumni Networks, 2004-2013 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Asian Cities Climate Change Resilience Network, 2012-2014 (Box 66, Folder 1-4, Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Asian Drivers, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Bellagio Series on Future of Development and Philanthropy, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Bellagio Series on Future of Development and Philanthropy, 2011 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Bus Rapid Transit, 2012 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Bus Rapid Transit, 2012 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Building American Democracy, 1996-1999 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Campaign for American Workers, 2006-2009 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Campaign for American Workers, 2006-2009 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2080
    - Program and Policy - Campaign for American Workers - Supplementary Material (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Care Works, 2011 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Catalyzing the New Mobility, 2011 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Catalyzing and Scaling Impact Enterprises, 2012 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Cities and Information, 2010 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Cities and Information, 2010 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2081
    - Program and Policy - Civil Society, 1989-2012 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Civil Society, 1989-2012 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Program and Policy - Climate Change Initiative - Front of File, 2009-2011 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Program and Policy - Climate Change Initiative, 2009-2013 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Climate Change Initiative, 2006-2008 (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Climate Change Initiative - Supplementary Material, 2007 (Box 72, Folder 4, Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Climate Smart Rural Development for Africa, 2010-2011 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Communication for Social Change, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Communication for Social Change, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2071